topbrowserbasedgames.com 2017-11-12

# Privacy Policy - TopBrowserBasedGames - Free To Play Browser Games

This Privacy Policy applies to the use of the website [www.topbrowserbasedgames.com](http://www.topbrowserbasedgames.com/) and all other services provided by BlackCap Media GmbH & Co. KG, Kettelerstr. 3-11, 97222 Rimpar, Germany, e.g. application services, and addresses all users of our website and services.

At BlackCap Media we treat your data with responsibility and in accordance with the provisions of German Data Protection Law in particular the German Data Protection Act (Bundesdatenschutzgesetz, BDSG) and the Telemedia Act (Telemediengesetz, TMG). With this Privacy Policy BlackCap Media provides a review of all information regarding the collection, processing, usage and protection of your data while using our website and services as well as your means of obtaining information about your data.

**_1.Data collection, processing and use_**

We collect as little data as possible. However, in order to run and improve our services following applies:

**Contact / Contractual Information:** We only collect personal data, i.e. data in connection to a determined or determinable person for example name, address, email, phone number, when you provide it voluntarily to us especially via a special form on our website or via email. We collect the following personal data: name, email, subject  of inquiry and any other personal data you may provide to us voluntarily.

The personal data will be exclusively used for processing our business relationships with you, fulfilling contractual obligations and transact the whole business with you and answering to your inquiry. No personal data provided by you will be made available to third parties unless this transfer is stated in this Privacy Policy and compliant with German Data Protection Law.

BlackCap Media provides newsletters. We only send you our newsletter after your explicit prior consent. At any time you have the possibility to contradict the receipt of our newsletter via email to [privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com](mailto:privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com) or means provided in every newsletter email. By giving us your consent you explicitly agree in the usage of your provided data for the means of us sending you our newsletter.

**Analysing / Tracking / Advertising:** In order to run, measure and improve our services and fulfill our contractual duties BlackCap Media collects anonymized usage data when you use our website and services. For this purpose we collect information about user IP address, country, language, device, user-agent, browser name and version, visit counts, operating system name and version , the referring url of the page linking to us and the usage time. We use this usage data for system-relevant and statistic purposes and do not make them available to third parties without your written authorization.

In order to determine the profitability of the individual promotional campaigns for the advertisement we run, we also save information about campaigns and placements of ads. In detail we collect data regarding the name of the campaign, the website that contains our campaign and the advertisement.

Especially for tracking purposes our website and services use so called “Cookies” and “Unique Transactions Identifiers” for Server2Server Postback Tracking that are passed through via urls to track a transaction. Cookies are minor amounts of data in form of text information that are sent to your browser via a server and served on your hard drive (“persistent cookies”) or your computer’s Random Access Memory (“session cookies”). The former cookies remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time while we do not connect any personal data with such cookies, the latter cookies time out by closing your browser window. You have the ability to decide about letting a webserver place cookies in your Internet browser’s settings. We would like to inform you that some features of our website or services may not be available if you do not accept cookies.

We hereby inform you that by clicking on an advertisement or a link you might be referred from our website or services to the website or service of the respective advertiser for the campaign or respective other third party. From the moment you leave our website or services we are no longer responsible for processing, handling and security of data that is collected by third parties especially an advertiser you were referred to. Please refer to the Privacy Policy of the respective advertiser for further information about the handling of your newly collected data from that point on.

As you browse TopBrowserBasedGames.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partners, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with TopBrowserBasedGames.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  
To opt out from those services please use links below: AdRoll: [Visit opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)  
Facebook:[Visit opt out page](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/)

**Transfer to Officials:**  In individual cases we are entitled to provide information about data by order of the competent authority to the extent that is necessary for purposes of law enforcement, protection against threats to public safety by the police authorities of the countries, to fulfill the statutory duties of the constitutional protection authorities of the Federation and the Länder, the Federal Intelligence Service or the Military or for the enforcement of intellectual property rights.

**_2.Data security_**

We at BlackCap Media protect your personal data adequately by different means of security measures. Physical, procedural and technical measures are used to protect our databases and guarantee the handling of your personal data only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. We cannot ascertain complete data security for communications via email or mobile communications services.

**_3. ** _User’s rights and Privacy Policy’s changes_**_**

At any time you have the right to obtain information about the stored personal data regarding your person, their source and potential recipient, the purpose of storage and processing and erasure or blocking of your data. If further information is required or the deletion of user data is desired, contact us under [privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com](mailto:privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com).

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without prior notification as we deem necessary. Please hold yourself informed about possible modifications by visiting this page from time to time. deletion of the user data is desired, contact us under[privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com](mailto:privacy@topbrowserbasedgames.com).
